[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"After training , Bush kept flying , racking up hundreds of hours in F - 102 jets .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the participant \"Bush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I like yuor blog .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"like\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Meats are kept VERY cold , seafood smells fresh and the serving bar is VERY clean .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"smells\", does the participant \"seafood\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think it s only fair that nowadays every town should provide at least one halal cafe or restaurant and hopefully one day every British catering establishment will be halal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Across the United States , the northern edge of species ' range is expanding , \" she said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"she\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I did an overnight in a home stay that was sweet and the water market was wonderful .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The letter bombs were sent in connection with the treatment of the Egyptian islamists imprisoned for the earlier attack on the WTC and a related plot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"bombs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Claude Mandil , the executive director of the International Energy Agency in Paris , said the reserves in the East China Sea were hardly worth the trouble .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Mandil\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His one - day mission vaulted his communist homeland into the elite circle of spacefaring nations - Russia and the United States - that can launch and sustain humans in space .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vaulted\", does the participant \"mission\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In a highly significant move Afghan Pashtun tribes along the Pakistan border warned the Taliban in Quetta and Chaman that if they try and disrupt the elections , they would be resisted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"disrupt\", does the participant \"elections\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I like to imagine the thought processes going on in W 's head if he were to actually read the letter , but it is hard to picture him actually reading this letter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"picture\", does the participant \"him\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Everything we ordered was prepared to perfection , and was presented perfectly .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Debbie said , it is going to be hard on me to sale my old dodge truck .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sale\", does the participant \"truck\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The hijacker Ahmed Alhaznawi appears to have contracted cutaneous anthrax in Afghanistan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"contracted\", does the participant \"anthrax\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I thought we only had cashout , at most 3 times , before this June .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ordered a kid meal with a milk and found a bottle was half opened already .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"meal\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These links present the many viewpoints that existed and still exist about the disaster called Chernobyl :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"present\", does the participant \"links\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"One thought is to have just the agenda as a couple topics and then lead in with the first two questions as I 've listed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"listed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I saw a site that charges $ 0.70 per mile .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the participant \"site\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The name was derived from the founder 's name Dr. Michael Cowpland .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"derived\", does the participant \"name\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They kill people .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kill\", does the participant \"people\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I knew I had found the real deal , big pies , sold by the slice , with the pizzas sitting under the glass in the front .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knew\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His press release following the hearing renewed the call for \" refunds . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"renewed\", does the participant \"call\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" At some point , Patricia tripped or the bear tripped her and was at her back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tripped\", does the participant \"her\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We need to change the lock and place posted signs at the gate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"place\", does the participant \"signs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"TEXAS ROADHOUSE HAS VERY GOOD MEALS , THAT THE MEAT COMES RIGHT OFF THE BONES .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"HAS\", does the participant \"MEALS\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The bear dwarfed the 6 - foot - 1 Mr. Parenteau , knocking him to the ground , he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dwarfed\", does the participant \"Parenteau\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He showed me the car I was interested in and we took a test drive .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"showed\", does the participant \"car\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The only neurological sign that he shows is that he barely drags his toes and sometimes has trouble with his right lead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"sign\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I hope all are well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Iran is encircled by Afghanistan , by the Gulf States , Iraq and the Moslem republics of the former Soviet Union .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"encircled\", does the participant \"Iran\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The other stylists around me kept pressuring me saying he 's so wonderful , you 're going to love your hair .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pressuring\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"he crawls on top of them but does not try to eat them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"crawls\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She gave me amazing pictures at an amazing price and made my wedding day so memorable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said it was the same tire , and verified this , after checking both the actual tire on my car and my service papers from earlier in the week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Either I suck at my own style or Janice is a genius .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suck\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As concerned citizens we affirm the liberty of adults of the same gender to love and marry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"affirm\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I sent this to Mary last week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"this\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"That means they are fighting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fighting\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Plans are to build a private pipeline to Equilon 's West Delta # 143 platform and then bring the oil onshore .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"build\", does the participant \"pipeline\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Ten Degree Channel divides the Andamans , which are the larger and more heavily populated northern islands , from the 20 or so Nicobar Islands in the south .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"divides\", does the participant \"Channel\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Their sense of humour and calmness when dealing with the little ones amazes me every time I walk in .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"walk\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They sent over someone who said he knows nothing about curtains and could not show me fabric options or give an estimate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"show\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Only Caucasians had any political power , corporate presence or owned businesses except for Mom and Pop stores in some neighborhoods .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"power\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I want to apply for canada skilled immigeration program .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You said you liked her and she accepted it as a truth and perhaps as a compliment , but it does not mean she fancies you or wants to pair off with you .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accepted\", does the participant \"she\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There are special regions uniquely and imposingly designed for the children .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"regions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A key question is how they acquired the anthrax strain first isolated by the Texas Veterinary Medical Diagnostic Lab in 1980 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"acquired\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The pictures are broadcast at a rate of about 60 Hz , which is how fast they need to move for us to see them as a moving , flawless picture .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broadcast\", does the participant \"pictures\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"For weeks , reporters scoured Alabama in search of pilots or anyone who might have remembered seeing Mr. Bush at the time he was serving in the National Guard there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"scoured\", does the participant \"Alabama\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The German Expressionist movement was destroyed as a result .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"destroyed\", does the participant \"movement\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The prestigious IAEA ( International Atomic Energy Agency ) published an early report on Chernobyl which was based on information from Russian sources and stated that there was no significant health effects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"published\", does the participant \"IAEA\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We sued Houston Casualty last year but I do n't recall making any bad faith claims .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sued\", does the participant \"Casualty\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A lack of organisation , coupled with the distain for its customers , makes this the worst rental agency I have used .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"this\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They sell feed and milk bottles at the front and I recommend you buy lots .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sell\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sussexs have soft feathers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"feathers\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I used to eat at places like New China or Green Buffet in Troy , MO - nothing terrible but not that great .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"meet\", does the participant \"obligation\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Michele Tollis , Fabio 's father , began to attend metal concerts and festivals across Europe , handing out leaflets and quizzing Fabio 's friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"began\", does the participant \"Tollis\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It 's located in the huge HONKA Log Homes building , by Walmart off of Evergreen Parkway .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"located\", does the participant \"It\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Saddam killed every month more people than all those who died from suicide murders since the Coalition occupation of Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"those\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have the best prices locally and good customer service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"prices\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Attached are the draft Schedule to the ISDA Master Agreement , together with Paragraph 13 to the ISDA Credit Support Annex .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"Schedule\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They both went to jail and a new manager was put in charge of the apartments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"went\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Lee Huber made the same request last year and we gave her the chair ( she only wanted one , however ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Huber\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I left with a case of BRAWLER !!!! !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I thought that I had gained my cockatiel 's trust , but now he 's not coming to me when I open his cage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gained\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I signed up with one of the staff who was very pleasant and professional .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"signed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a conversation with the woman running this place in April 2010 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know you are very worried , but getting her to the vet is the best thing you can do for her .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His co-workers love him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"co-workers\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( News assistant Bobby Bender recalls the letter containing the items to have been addressed to The Sun . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recalls\", does the participant \"letter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My boyfriend and I were woken up in the middle of the night at our campsite by drunken kids who 'd arrived around 1:00 am and were drinking at the springs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"woken\", does the participant \"boyfriend\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He thinks he will deceive people in this way , so that the real McCartney will not be perceived .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deceive\", does the participant \"people\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I believe he must have waited among the gorse bushes through which the path winds and struck him down as he passed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think they 'll send us another update once he 's out of emergency and into a room .?\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ended up paying much more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paying\", does the participant \"more\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is this circle that makes sure that women remain inferior , that democracy is unthinkable and that exposure to the outside world is minimal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remain\", does the participant \"women\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They wanted to brainwash them and control them . ''\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brainwash\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I found them and purchased both from a gallery in London , William Weston .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchased\", does the participant \"both\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called them for an estimate and they INSULTED ME WHEN I ASK THEM QUESTIONS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As faith leaders , we commit ourselves to public action , visibility , education , and mutual support in the service of the right and freedom to marry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commit\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had a large party , about fifty people or so , and yet everything was served quickly and we all had a wonderful time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"By comparison , outdoor cats have a life expectancy of 3 - 7 years depending on how many predators are in the local environment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cats\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We felt we made it better because it introduced a process for review and refund . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"introduced\", does the participant \"process\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"All of the doors tend to look alike and having ' something ' on your door helps you and your kids find your room easier .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tend\", does the participant \"All\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" You say , ' wow ! '\"\nQuestion: In the event \"say\", does the participant \"You\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The IPN report examines commercial fish species , but it neglects important non-commercial animals , such as seals and polar bears .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"neglects\", does the participant \"animals\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Police and prosecutors have the tools .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"Police\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"EVERYTHING IN HERE SEEMS TO AMAZE ME !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"SEEMS\", does the participant \"EVERYTHING\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The plants provide shade and root strength for bank stability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"plants\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"address\", does the participant \"rights\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"On top of things , I had quiz at 8 am .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I work for a large retail company recently expanding our operations into Canada and had to travel to ensure all of our computer network equipment was installed properly and on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"work\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I purchased a 2 - year old certified pre-owned BMW from this dealership .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchased\", does the participant \"BMW\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a routine surgery for an ingrown toenail .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"surgery\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I hope your dad 's surgery goes well !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Some conservationists want the protection extended so wolves can move into other states , including Colorado , Utah and Oregon , among others .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"protection\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But today , I got a boy and realized that he is HUGE !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"boy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yet people seem willing -- even eager -- to accommodate mountain lions , despite the risks .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accommodate\", does the participant \"lions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}]